gamerpig.com 2016-06-25

# GamerPig - Privacy Policy

GamerPig is committed to protecting your privacy online. In order to ensure our commitment, we have adopted an online privacy policy that directs how we collect, store, and use information collected about you online.

## What information does GamerPig collect?

GamerPig may request and/or collect non-private information from you when you use GamerPig.com and/or register. To protect your privacy, we ask that you avoid sending us any and all personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

GamerPig may use cookies to improve the usability of our website. A "cookie" is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to give you the most personal experience possible on our website. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. We never use cookies to store personally identifiable information. Additionally, GamerPig may use cookies and third party vendors to deliver ads related to GamerPig to you while you are surfing other websites. If you would like to opt-out of such ads, you may visit <https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> to opt-out of such use of cookies.

## IP addresses

GamerPig may collect your IP address for the purpose of safety and security.

## Log files

Other non-personal information collected by GamerPig is in the form of logs-files that record website activity, including how many "hits" a particular web page is getting (a.k.a., "click-through data"). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks the "Home" icon on our site. These entries enable GamerPig to assess overall site activity, and improve the general user experience. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain information about your system such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer) and the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS).

## Linking to third party sites

GamerPig may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites. We strongly recommend our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information to them. GamerPig assumes no responsibility for the content found on third party websites linked from GamerPig.com. GamerPig hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site.

## Advertisements on GamerPig

GamerPig allows the use of advertising on GamerPig.com by third party advertisers. Some of these advertising partners use cookies or similar technologies to better measure their campaign effectiveness, to target future campaigns and to better deliver a targeted experience to users. Advertisers must comply with personal data guidelines. All advertisers are instructed by GamerPig not to display ads with sexual, violent or drug & alcohol related themes as well as anything that would be considered objectionable by societal norms. Should you find an inappropriate or offensive advertisement on GamerPig, please notify us by emailing [contact@gamerpig.com](mailto:contact@gamerpig.com). Additionally, third parties may collect certain types of information about your visits to GamerPig, including how you interact with the content on GamerPig.

For more information about best practices in Network Advertising, see [NAI code of conduct](http://www.networkadvertising.org/2013_Principles.pdf).

### Google Adsense

Some of the advertisements may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to GamerPig.com and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

## General

By using this site, you signify your assent to the GamerPig.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check the updates regularly so you are updated on these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance. Our goal is that you have a great experience and we continue to deliver great content to you on GamerPig. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, feel free to approach us on [contact@gamerpig.com](mailto:contact@gamerpig.com).

This document was last updated February 2, 2015
